quickjobfinder.net 2004-04-15

# Quick Job Finder

**Introduction**

As a Web site dedicated to providing career opportunities and information, we balance privacy concerns with candidates' requirements to make their qualifications and availability known to employers.

We collect personally identifying information about you only when you specifically and knowingly provide it to us.

**Basic Statement**

Personally identifying information that you provide will not be made available to third parties outside of our network without your explicit permission.

We collect personally identifying information about you only when you specifically and knowingly provide it to us. Your personally identifying information will be used to personalize your experience within us, or for such other purposes as are described at any point where we collect this information from you.

We may make aggregate information about our customers (e.g. overall statistics) available to third parties for advertising and other purposes. Information that personally identifies you will be kept strictly confidential unless you specifically authorize it to be made available, as in the case of resumés and profiles.

Personally identifying information which you choose to provide to another party or Web site will be subject to their privacy policy. For example, if you send your resumé to an employer or recruiter you found while searching our site, information you provide to that party is subject to their privacy policy rather than ours.

**What Is Personally Identifying Information?**

Personally identifying information is information that can be explicitly used to identify and/or contact you as an individual. This includes, information like your real name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, etc. Information that, by itself, cannot be explicitly linked with your real identity is not considered personally identifying. Examples of this are favourite or bookmarked Web sites, or your preferences with respect to how you wish to see a given page or site set up according to the selections you choose.

On occasion, we may ask you for personal information such as your name or address. We do this when you register for contests/promotions or services that require registration or subscription. We need to collect this information for fulfilling prizes, and for tracking/verifying compliance with our policies. It may also be needed for purposes of compliance with federal, provincia/statel and local laws and/or for editorial and feedback solicitation purposes. When we intend to use your personal information, we tell you up front. This way you can decide whether you want to give us the information or not.

**Links To Other Sites**

Users should be aware that when you are on our site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites that take you outside our service. For example, if you click on a banner advertisement, the click takes you off our site. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use the our logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. Always be aware of where you end up!

Our policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond our control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.

**E-Mail To Us**

When you send us e-mail, we will use your name and e-mail address only to respond to the concerns you write to us with. Your e-mail may be shared with appropriate people within the organization to help us respond to your concerns and improve the service.

**Changes To This Policy**

From time to time, we may introduce new products and services to its users and members. We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time by notifying customers, via our site, of a new privacy policy. You can send e-mail to support with any further questions.
